{
	"adults": [
		{
			"name": "Jeremy",
			"fullName": "Jeremy Gabriel Moritz",
			"birthday": "1981-06-30"
		},
		{
			"name": "Christine",
			"fullName": "Christine Marie Moritz",
			"birthday": "1981-03-17"
		}
	],
	"kids": [
		{
			"name": "Angel",
			"fullName": "Angela Brianne Moritz",
			"birthday": "2004-09-18",
			"questionnaires": [
				{
					"qDate": "2012-05-18",
					"questions": [
						{
							"rating": 1,
							"question": "What is your happiest memory?",
							"answer": "When i got to go to the store with Grandpa and he bought my Ariel doll."
						},
						{
							"rating": 3,
							"question": "Why do you like being a kid?",
							"answer": "You're still in school, and you don't do all those adultish things like pay bills and have an account in the bank."
						},
						{
							"rating": 1,
							"question": "One word to describe you would be _______.",
							"answer": "Humble."
						},
						{
							"rating": 3,
							"question": "What advice would you give your parents?",
							"answer": "I would tell Daddy to work at the house like mommy does."
						},
						{
							"rating": 2,
							"question": "If you could be any animal, which one would you be and why?",
							"answer": "I'd be a black pony because I think black looks like a good color on a horse, and I also think baby ponies are cute."
						},
						{
							"rating": 1,
							"question": "What do you like to do for fun?",
							"answer": "Let's see... school work... my big book... watching TV... creating Mr. Quacker."
						},
						{
							"rating": 2,
							"question": "Tell about a funny time in your life.",
							"answer": "When I was reading quotes from the kids."
						},
						{
							"rating": 1,
							"question": "What is your favorite thing to do? Why?",
							"answer": "Creating Mr. Quacker.  Because Mr. Quacker is a cute ducky, and it was my first ducky."
						},
						{
							"rating": 1,
							"question": "What is your favorite thing to do with your friends?",
							"answer": "Playing Barbies probably."
						},
						{
							"rating": 3,
							"question": "What do you love most about your siblings?",
							"answer": "Harmony and Charity: playful. Tony: awesome."
						},
						{
							"rating": 2,
							"question": "What was the nicest thing you did for someone?",
							"answer": "I'm guessing it would be like helping Grandpa with the babies."
						},
						{
							"rating": 3,
							"question": "What do you think you will be doing 10 years from now?",
							"answer": "Doing a whole whole bunch of musicals and going to college."
						},
						{
							"rating": 1,
							"question": "What is your favorite thing to do in the summer?",
							"answer": "Go swimming!"
						},
						{
							"rating": 3,
							"question": "What would be the ideal allowance? Tell me how you would use it.",
							"answer": "I would have $40/week... actually, I'd get $100/week!  And I would go to the Disney Store, and buy the dazzling, dazzling Rapunzel doll that was $100.  I'd waste all my money on that!  Actually, I would because she's beautiful."
						},
						{
							"rating": 2,
							"question": "What do you think makes a person good-looking?",
							"answer": "A kind heart."
						},
						{
							"rating": 1,
							"question": "Name two things we should do as a family on the weekend.",
							"answer": "Go to Lego Land, and go to Science City."
						},
						{
							"rating": 3,
							"question": "What is the grossest thing you can think of?",
							"answer": "That would be Zombie Cafe (iPad game), when they serve a lump of green stuff and grossness."
						},
						{
							"rating": 3,
							"question": "What would you do with $1000?",
							"answer": "If I had $1000, I would first tithe, then I would spend $100 of it on a really, really expensive Barbie.  And I would spend another part of it at a garage sale, then I would donate some of it, then I would tithe again... I think.... I wouldn't donate it.... I would take the donate half, and I would give it to my mother and father!  All done."
						},
						{
							"rating": 2,
							"question": "What do you want to be when you grow up?",
							"answer": "I want to be a designer because I like how you make clothes and fabrics and stuff."
						},
						{
							"rating": 3,
							"question": "How do you think peanut butter is made?",
							"answer": "With peanuts, and I know it’s not made with butter.  They smash the peanuts, take out the acid, and put the acid in the peanut butter jar."
						},
						{
							"rating": 1,
							"question": "How tall is Daddy?",
							"answer": "Umm… 20 feet tall?"
						},
						{
							"rating": 1,
							"question": "How tall is Mommy?",
							"answer": "Oh I know I know!  10 feet tall."
						},
						{
							"rating": 2,
							"question": "What does Daddy do at work?",
							"answer": "I know what you do at work!  You work on Rhythm City and ask people to buy the DVD."
						},
						{
							"rating": 2,
							"question": "How do you think shows get onto the TV?",
							"answer": "on Netflix and the internet.  I think shows get on Netflix I think it’s because… I’m just saying all the wrong words… I bet it’s because people let them use their shows on Netflix, and Netflix would pay them to let them use their shows."
						},
						{
							"rating": 3,
							"question": "Why do you think God put you in our family?",
							"answer": "Because I fit in well, and I’m really good with little kids"
						},
						{
							"rating": 2,
							"question": "Why do you think the sky is blue?",
							"answer": "I think the sky is blue because it goes well with the grass.  Blue and green go good together."
						}
					]
				},
				{
					"qDate": "2014-08-17",
					"questions": [
						{
							"rating": 2,
							"question": "If you could spend your time doing only one activity, what would that activity be? Why?",
							"answer": "Mmm...it would be….that's a hard one...I would go across the world singing because I think it would be fun singing for a lot of people. And I like singing."
						},
						{
							"rating": 1,
							"question": "If you could learn how to do something new next week, what would you choose? Why?",
							"answer": "I would choose learning how to play the guitar because I've always wanted to learn and I think it would be fun to sing along while I played."
						},
						{
							"rating": 3,
							"question": "If you could do something to cheer up a group of kids less fortunate than you, what would you do? Why?",
							"answer": "Anything? I would get them a big dinner and give them the leftovers to take home."
						},
						{
							"rating": 3,
							"question": "If you could pick something in your bedroom that would last forever, what would you choose? Why?",
							"answer": "My baptismal plaque because it would always remind me that I  made a commitment to Jesus and that He's my savior."
						},
						{
							"rating": 3,
							"question": "If you could send an e-mail or text message to anyone in the world knowing that they would in fact open it and read it, to whom would you send it? What would you say? Why?",
							"answer": "Well, I would send it to...ok, so, if they could read it, I would send it to Harmony and Charity and I would say \"Harmony and Charity, you are amazeballs sisters and I'm glad you're in my family.\" And I would put bubbles and hearts and butterflies all over it."
						},
						{
							"rating": 3,
							"question": "If you could have a super power, what would you choose to have? Why? What super-hero name would you choose?",
							"answer": "I would probably choose teleportation and teleport to different places in time; because if I had teleportation, I would be able to tell what happened with Adam and Eve, and ride with Noah's ark, and see all the big scary giants in the Promised Land.  And I'd go 100 years in the future to see what the technology is like; my name would be...when I play with Adam, it's always Emma….but I'd choose The Incredible Girl...unless it's already taken."
						},
						{
							"rating": 2,
							"question": "If you could have any animal in the world and shrink it down to a mouse-sized pet, what animal would you choose? Why? What name would you give it? Why?",
							"answer": "I would choose a tiger because if I shrunk a tiger it wouldn't hurt if it bit me.  And I'd be able to keep it in a small, enclosed space and be able to play with it.  I would name it Batman because it has black stripes."
						},
						{
							"rating": 1,
							"question": "Where do you think would be the most exciting place in the United States to live? To visit? How about in the world?",
							"answer": "Live: Beverly Hills, CA.  Or Disneyworld.  Visit: Hollywood.  World: Either Paris or Italy"
						},
						{
							"rating": 1,
							"question": "Can you think of three things we could do to make meals together more interesting and fun for everyone in the family?",
							"answer": "We could ... umm... not sure."
						},
						{
							"rating": 2,
							"question": "What is the silliest thing you've ever done? What would you like to do to top it? Why?",
							"answer": "I came up with the word, \"MERF!\"; To top it, I would paint my face like a clown and then go around giving everyone hugs."
						},
						{
							"rating": 2,
							"question": "What is your favorite sport or game? If you could change one rule, what would you change? Why?",
							"answer": "Cheerleading; ...I can't change cheerleading rules! How about chess? I'd make it so that every time Tony and I played other people, our queens could move any way she wanted."
						},
						{
							"rating": 2,
							"question": "If you could design the perfect play space for yourself, what would it have in it? Where would it be?",
							"answer": "In my space, I would have a piano and a guitar and music books.  I'd also have a karaoke system, an ipad mini, and an iPod 4.  I'd have big blow up balloons of my siblings.  I'd also have a big disco ball that you could turn on and off with a light switch. And there would be special light switches marked yellow, orange, red, green, and purple to make the room change colors."
						},
						{
							"rating": 1,
							"question": "What is the strangest sound you can make? What do you think it sounds the most like in nature?",
							"answer": "*makes high pitched noise* *makes weird clicking noise* I think it sounds most like a dolphin. I was going to say cicada, but it doesn't sound like that."
						},
						{
							"rating": 1,
							"question": "What part about being a kid do you think you will miss the most when you grow up? Why? What do you think I/we (the adults) miss the most? Why did you choose that?",
							"answer": "That I didn't have to pay bills and my parents took care of me. Because I don't want to use money to pay bill.  I want to buy leisurely items.  I'd way rather spend it on an expensive bedspread.  And not everyone will be as splendid as my parents. You and Daddy miss not having to pay bills, but I know you and Daddy like your jobs. I think if you got the opportunity, you'd go on a missions trip to teach kids piano for free."
						},
						{
							"rating": 3,
							"question": "What is your favorite word right now? What do you like about it? When have you used it recently?",
							"answer": "MERF!? Because merf is an awesome word.  And it's my word.  And Maggie's word.  Case closed."
						},
						{
							"rating": 2,
							"question": "If you could swap places with anyone in the world for just a day, who would you choose? Why?",
							"answer": "An unmarried princess.  I don't really know of any that are unmarried, cause I only know of one princess.  I want to see how princesses live and see if their lives are as hard as everyone says they are."
						},
						{
							"rating": 1,
							"question": "What do you think would be the best thing about being a dog or cat? Why? What would be the worst thing? Why?",
							"answer": "The best thing about being a dog would be sprinting for a long time without gettting tired and I'd get played with a lot.  The worst would be having black and white eyesight and having to eat disgusting dog food.  The worst part of being a cat would be barfing hairballs a lot."
						},
						{
							"rating": 1,
							"question": "If you could double the time you spend on just one subject in school, what would you choose? Why? What subject would you give up in order to do that? Why?",
							"answer": "Reading, because I really like reading.  It feeds my brain information I didn't know before. I'd would probably give up science or social studies."
						},
						{
							"rating": 2,
							"question": "What is the most awesome thing you've ever seen? What made it so awesome?",
							"answer": "Seeing someone stand on a pole while doing tricks with a soccer ball. It was amazing that he was able to stand on one foot and balance while he was moving the ball around his leg and dribbling it on top of his head.  It was amazing."
						},
						{
							"rating": 2,
							"question": "What is one thing that you think you will definitely be great at when you are an adult? Why?",
							"answer": "READING! Because I'm already great at it and it would be kind of hard to learn how to read really, really well and then forget how to read."
						}
					]
				}
			]
		},
		{
			"name": "Tony",
			"fullName": "Anthony Jacob Moritz",
			"birthday": "2006-01-02",
			"questionnaires": [
				{
					"qDate": "2012-05-18",
					"questions": [
						{
							"rating": 1,
							"question": "What is your happiest memory?",
							"answer": "The first time I met Noah (church friend)."
						},
						{
							"rating": 1,
							"question": "Why do you like being a kid?",
							"answer": "Because you have toys, and you can play video games, and candy."
						},
						{
							"rating": 2,
							"question": "One word to describe you would be _______.",
							"answer": "That I was born."
						},
						{
							"rating": 3,
							"question": "What advice would you give your parents?",
							"answer": "Give us lunch."
						},
						{
							"rating": 2,
							"question": "If you could be any animal, which one would you be and why?",
							"answer": "T-Rex, and it's because they're cool, and they're strong, and they're tall."
						},
						{
							"rating": 1,
							"question": "What do you like to do for fun?",
							"answer": "Play with my friends."
						},
						{
							"rating": 2,
							"question": "Tell about a funny time in your life.",
							"answer": "A book that Angel and me read at night – Nursery rhymes.  We read it in different languages, so it's more funny."
						},
						{
							"rating": 2,
							"question": "What is your favorite thing to do? Why?",
							"answer": "Play on the iPad, because it has a whole bunch of games that I like."
						},
						{
							"rating": 1,
							"question": "What is your favorite thing to do with your friends?",
							"answer": "Play Star Wars and Batman Avengers and stuff."
						},
						{
							"rating": 2,
							"question": "What do you love most about your siblings? ",
							"answer": "Angel plays with me a lot.  Charity walks up to me a lot.  And Harmony? ... That sometimes Harmony plays with me."
						},
						{
							"rating": 2,
							"question": "What was the nicest thing you did for someone?",
							"answer": "I played with my friends when they asked me."
						},
						{
							"rating": 3,
							"question": "What do you think you will be doing 10 years from now?",
							"answer": "I would be in High School, and I will do homework and I'm gonna have to have lunch money."
						},
						{
							"rating": 1,
							"question": "What is your favorite thing to do in the summer?",
							"answer": "Um... go at the pool."
						},
						{
							"rating": 3,
							"question": "What would be the ideal allowance? Tell me how you would use it.",
							"answer": "I would say $30, and I would buy that toy spider web gun."
						},
						{
							"rating": 1,
							"question": "What do you think makes a person good-looking?",
							"answer": "When their hair looks nice; when they have nice clothes on."
						},
						{
							"rating": 2,
							"question": "Name two things we should do as a family on the weekend.",
							"answer": "We could go to a special place to eat, and we could go to Lego Land together."
						},
						{
							"rating": 3,
							"question": "What is the grossest thing you can think of?",
							"answer": "Looking at dirty dishes."
						},
						{
							"rating": 3,
							"question": "What would you do with $1000?",
							"answer": "I would buy food, video games, and toys, and a house... like a skyscraper if I could."
						},
						{
							"rating": 3,
							"question": "What do you want to be when you grow up?",
							"answer": "A police officer, because they get a lot of money, and they save people, and they take villains to jail, and they have a light car... ya know, those lights... and they have a little thing that tells how fast cars are going, and they have computers."
						},
						{
							"rating": 2,
							"question": "How tall is Daddy?",
							"answer": "Umm… 10 feet tall? … Oh I’m guessing daddy’s 12 feet tall"
						},
						{
							"rating": 1,
							"question": "How tall is Mommy?",
							"answer": "10 feet tall"
						},
						{
							"rating": 1,
							"question": "What does Daddy do at work?",
							"answer": "You work on the internet."
						},
						{
							"rating": 3,
							"question": "How do you think shows get onto the TV?",
							"answer": "Um… um like if someone’s a superstar then people can put it on a commercial and get things on internets and put it on Netflix."
						},
						{
							"rating": 2,
							"question": "Why do you think God put you in our family?",
							"answer": "Because he wanted to because he knew that I’d be good for you."
						},
						{
							"rating": 1,
							"question": "Why do you think the sky is blue?",
							"answer": "Because Jesus is creative and he wanted to paint the sky blue."
						}
					]
				},
				{
					"qDate": "2014-08-17",
					"questions": [
						{
							"rating": 1,
							"question": "If you could spend your time doing only one activity, what would that activity be? Why?",
							"answer": "Playing video games because it entertains me."
						},
						{
							"rating": 3,
							"question": "If you could learn how to do something new next week, what would you choose? Why?",
							"answer": "Kinda would want to learn a sport... \"What sport?\" Oh...whatever sport."
						},
						{
							"rating": 2,
							"question": "If you could do something to cheer up a group of kids less fortunate than you, what would you do? Why?",
							"answer": "I would give the orphanage money and um... hand out presents for them."
						},
						{
							"rating": 1,
							"question": "If you could pick something in your bedroom that would last forever, what would you choose? Why?",
							"answer": "Legos.  No reason."
						},
						{
							"rating": 3,
							"question": "If you could send an e-mail or text message to anyone in the world knowing that they would in fact open it and read it, to whom would you send it? What would you say? Why?",
							"answer": "To my Dad.  It would say: \"Dad, I love you.\"  Why? Because I love you."
						},
						{
							"rating": 2,
							"question": "If you could have a super power, what would you choose to have? Why? What super-hero name would you choose?",
							"answer": "Invincibility. Because I couldn't get hurt and I would never die. I would be named Invincible Man."
						},
						{
							"rating": 3,
							"question": "If you could have any animal in the world and shrink it down to a mouse-sized pet, what animal would you choose? Why? What name would you give it? Why?",
							"answer": "I would choose a dinosaur, because if it was small it would be easy to take out its teeth."
						},
						{
							"rating": 3,
							"question": "Where do you think would be the most exciting place in the United States to live? To visit? How about in the world?",
							"answer": "Canada.  Because it has Disneyworld there.  Doesn't it have Disneyworld there?  \"To visit?\"  Florida.  \"In the whole world?\" Kansas.  Because my friends are here."
						},
						{
							"rating": 1,
							"question": "Can you think of three things we could do to make meals together more interesting and fun for everyone in the family?",
							"answer": "Able to let the kids make it theirself but with help if they wanted."
						},
						{
							"rating": 3,
							"question": "What is the silliest thing you've ever done? What would you like to do to top it? Why?",
							"answer": "When I was two, I went up to my mom and said a bunch of random stuff in gibberish, and she didn't know what I was saying, and she answered \"Really?\" and I said \"Uh huh!\" and I got all happy and stuff.  \"Top It?\"  I don't know."
						},
						{
							"rating": 3,
							"question": "What is your favorite sport or game? If you could change one rule, what would you change? Why?",
							"answer": "Basketball and if it would be a game, it would also be Minecraft.  I wouldn't say Roblox cuz it's a website.  If I could change one rule about basketball, I would say to make the rule that the youngest person named Tony on any team could make the team win whenever he wants."
						},
						{
							"rating": 2,
							"question": "If you could design the perfect play space for yourself, what would it have in it? Where would it be?",
							"answer": "It would have Xbox, Playstation 4, Nintendo 64, Wii U, Five controllers with motion plusses built inside, 5 nunchucks, TV, a sofa, and two lamps, and NES, and 4 wavebirds (controllers), and a fan, and a bed.  Oh wait! And a carpet.  Where would it be?  On the right side of my house."
						},
						{
							"rating": 1,
							"question": "What is the strangest sound you can make? What do you think it sounds the most like in nature?",
							"answer": "Uh... that's hard because you'd just put a bunch of words to describe it. (makes a choking/swallowing/grunting sound)."
						},
						{
							"rating": 2,
							"question": "What part about being a kid do you think you will miss the most when you grow up? Why? What do you think I/we (the adults) miss the most? Why did you choose that?",
							"answer": "That I didn't have to work every day.  What do you think we miss the most? The first thing that popped up into my head is that we don't get to see our mom and dad so much.  I think it's something else though."
						},
						{
							"rating": 3,
							"question": "What is your favorite word right now? What do you like about it? When have you used it recently?",
							"answer": "Angel's would be \"Merf\" I know that.  Okay \"Cool.\"  That's what it is."
						},
						{
							"rating": 2,
							"question": "If you could swap places with anyone in the world for just a day, who would you choose? Why?",
							"answer": "I would want it to be someone close to my age I know that... Um... It would be Will (next door neighbor) just because I would understand his life more."
						},
						{
							"rating": 1,
							"question": "What do you think would be the best thing about being a dog or cat? Why? What would be the worst thing? Why?",
							"answer": "It would definitely be a dog... it's that you would be able to do a lot of... no... not that... just that you would have more energy and stuff so that you could run around faster and longer.  And you could do a lot of stuff that people couldn't do.  The worst thing?  Is that your owners feed you horrible tasting food."
						},
						{
							"rating": 2,
							"question": "If you could double the time you spend on just one subject in school, what would you choose? Why? What subject would you give up in order to do that? Why?",
							"answer": "Science. Because Science is easy because I only have to read two pages a day and the words are kinda big.  Subject to give up?  Math!  Because math takes a long ti... no wait.  I wouldn't give up math because math is important.  I would give up history because history mostly has myths, and I don't need to learn them."
						},
						{
							"rating": 1,
							"question": "What is the most awesome thing you've ever seen? What made it so awesome?",
							"answer": "A video of a motorcycle and a truck almost crashing but having like... well, I'm not sure if this is true, but it just might be true... and then an angel came to teleport him away."
						},
						{
							"rating": 2,
							"question": "What is one thing that you think you will definitely be great at when you are an adult? Why?",
							"answer": "Programming because I am getting taught programming now, so I will know a lot when I am a adult."
						}
					]
				}
			]
		},
		{
			"name": "Harmony",
			"fullName": "Harmony Grace Moritz",
			"birthday": "2009-02-09",
			"questionnaires": [
				{
					"qDate": "2012-05-18",
					"questions": [
						{
							"rating": 3,
							"question": "What is your happiest memory?",
							"answer": "My apple (that she's currently eating)."
						},
						{
							"rating": 2,
							"question": "Why do you like being a kid?",
							"answer": "Angel and Tony and Charity and Mommy and Daddy."
						},
						{
							"rating": 3,
							"question": "One word to describe you would be _______.",
							"answer": "Sad for my purple pony."
						},
						{
							"rating": 3,
							"question": "What advice would you give your parents?",
							"answer": "When I give you a present, it would be a pair of shoes for Daddy and a diamond ring for Mommy."
						},
						{
							"rating": 1,
							"question": "If you could be any animal, which one would you be and why?",
							"answer": "Elephant! (makes elephant noise)."
						},
						{
							"rating": 1,
							"question": "What do you like to do for fun?",
							"answer": "Play on my purple computer and my toys."
						},
						{
							"rating": 1,
							"question": "Tell about a funny time in your life.",
							"answer": "Birds eat me a lot and they poop a lot!"
						},
						{
							"rating": 2,
							"question": "What is your favorite thing to do? Why?",
							"answer": "Purple coffee.  It's hot so I can drink it."
						},
						{
							"rating": 1,
							"question": "What is your favorite thing to do with your friends?",
							"answer": "Play games. Like toss on the bed!"
						},
						{
							"rating": 3,
							"question": "What do you love most about your siblings? ",
							"answer": "Angel: a purple computer; Tony: flowers; Charity: getting lots of gummies in her mouth."
						},
						{
							"rating": 1,
							"question": "What was the nicest thing you did for someone?",
							"answer": "I gave them some treats ... like that."
						},
						{
							"rating": 2,
							"question": "What do you think you will be doing 10 years from now?",
							"answer": "Go to a church."
						},
						{
							"rating": 2,
							"question": "What is your favorite thing to do in the summer?",
							"answer": "Bubbles!"
						},
						{
							"rating": 2,
							"question": "What would be the ideal allowance? Tell me how you would use it.",
							"answer": "I would want $5 to buy a bunny."
						},
						{
							"rating": 2,
							"question": "What do you think makes a person good-looking?",
							"answer": "Getting married to a purple princess... like a prince."
						},
						{
							"rating": 1,
							"question": "Name two things we should do as a family on the weekend.",
							"answer": "A spit fight... and Rock Band!!"
						},
						{
							"rating": 1,
							"question": "What is the grossest thing you can think of?",
							"answer": "A yucky apple is yucky."
						},
						{
							"rating": 3,
							"question": "How do you think peanut butter is made?",
							"answer": "With sprinkles."
						},
						{
							"rating": 2,
							"question": "How tall is Daddy?",
							"answer": "Uh, big."
						},
						{
							"rating": 1,
							"question": "How tall is Mommy?",
							"answer": "Big!"
						},
						{
							"rating": 2,
							"question": "What does Daddy do at work?",
							"answer": "Uh, work... go to your office."
						},
						{
							"rating": 3,
							"question": "How does a tomato grow?",
							"answer": "Big beanstalk."
						},
						{
							"rating": 2,
							"question": "What do you think Yo Gabba Gabba do when they're not on TV?",
							"answer": "Like this! (starts dancing)"
						},
						{
							"rating": 1,
							"question": "Why do you think God put you in our family?",
							"answer": "Water give me, put me in my family."
						},
						{
							"rating": 3,
							"question": "What would you do with $1000?",
							"answer": "Uh... how about buy a bunny?  (\"Anything else?\") Nope."
						},
						{
							"rating": 3,
							"question": "What do you want to be when you grow up?",
							"answer": "Uh... a cow.... Is that a animal? (\"Yes.\") Uh, then I want to be a elephant."
						}
					]
				},
				{
					"qDate": "2014-08-17",
					"questions": [
						{
							"rating": 1,
							"question": "What is your happiest memory?",
							"answer": "Playing with Ava.  We don't see each other enough"
						},
						{
							"rating": 3,
							"question": "Why do you like being a kid?",
							"answer": "I'd rather be a princess instead"
						},
						{
							"rating": 1,
							"question": "One word to describe you would be _______.",
							"answer": "A dress"
						},
						{
							"rating": 1,
							"question": "What advice would you give your parents?",
							"answer": "That's a hard one..."
						},
						{
							"rating": 3,
							"question": "If you could be any animal, which one would you be and why?",
							"answer": "A unicorn. I mean a pony.  I would be a girl pony cuz they're so pretty. And I would name it jewels and put bows on her."
						},
						{
							"rating": 2,
							"question": "What do you like to do for fun?",
							"answer": "Play around. Play with my next door neighbor."
						},
						{
							"rating": 1,
							"question": "Tell about a funny time in your life.",
							"answer": "There's never a time when I joked a bit. Yeah! We're driving to college! Ok! We're driving to college. (inside joke, kinda)"
						},
						{
							"rating": 3,
							"question": "What is your favorite thing to do? Why?",
							"answer": "Be a star, because everynody will notice me and will cheer for me cuz I'm SUCH a star. And I wouldl make a cereal called \"Harmony's H's\".  And it would have marshmallows and the H's would have protein in them!"
						},
						{
							"rating": 2,
							"question": "What is your favorite thing to do with your friends?",
							"answer": "Play \"Just Dance\" with them"
						},
						{
							"rating": 2,
							"question": "What do you love most about your siblings?",
							"answer": "Angel: Playing with her..., Tony: Playing with him..., Charity: Playing with her..., Chase: Playing with him..., "
						},
						{
							"rating": 2,
							"question": "What was the nicest thing you did for someone?",
							"answer": "Be nice to them. That would be easy. Oh, wait! Make a necklace for them."
						},
						{
							"rating": 2,
							"question": "What do you think you will be doing 10 years from now?",
							"answer": "Uh, playing games. That was easy. Going to a Chick-fil-A opening."
						},
						{
							"rating": 1,
							"question": "What is your favorite thing to do in the summer?",
							"answer": "Go to the pool! Oh, and make it Schlitterbahn."
						},
						{
							"rating": 3,
							"question": "What would be the ideal allowance? Tell me how you would use it.",
							"answer": "$100. Buy stuff.  All the the toys in the world!...the girl toys. And I wish I had a fairy that could grant me one wish and it would be 1000 wishes! No, wait. Infinity wishes."
						},
						{
							"rating": 3,
							"question": "What do you think makes a person good-looking?",
							"answer": "Make-up"
						},
						{
							"rating": 1,
							"question": "Name two things we should do as a family on the weekend.",
							"answer": "Go to kids' museum and Aquarium"
						},
						{
							"rating": 3,
							"question": "What is the grossest thing you can think of?",
							"answer": "Oh let's see... a turtle? Those are SUPER GROSS! YUK!"
						}
					]
				}
			]
		},
		{
			"name": "Charity",
			"fullName": "Charity Jewel Moritz",
			"birthday": "2010-06-10",
			"questionnaires": [
				{
					"qDate": "2012-06-18",
					"questions": [
						{
							"rating": 1,
							"question": "What is your favorite cereal?",
							"answer": "Cereal and Eggs."
						},
						{
							"rating": 1,
							"question": "What's your favorite show?",
							"answer": "A Gabba Gabba! (Yo Gabba Gabba!)"
						},
						{
							"rating": 3,
							"question": "What do you want to be when you grow up?",
							"answer": "Mickey Mouse!"
						},
						{
							"rating": 3,
							"question": "What's your favorite thing about being a kid?",
							"answer": "Mimi's house!"
						},
						{
							"rating": 3,
							"question": "What advice would you give your parents?",
							"answer": "Blow bubbles."
						},
						{
							"rating": 1,
							"question": "What's your favorite thing to do?",
							"answer": "A Charity, a Harmony, a Davey."
						},
						{
							"rating": 1,
							"question": "What would you do with $1000?",
							"answer": "Please."
						},
						{
							"rating": 1,
							"question": "What do you like to play?",
							"answer": "Go ride."
						},
						{
							"rating": 2,
							"question": "What is your happiest memory?",
							"answer": "Daddy and Mommy and um um a Charity."
						},
						{
							"rating": 1,
							"question": "Why do you like being a kid?",
							"answer": "Charity."
						},
						{
							"rating": 1,
							"question": "One word to describe you would be _______.",
							"answer": "Self."
						},
						{
							"rating": 3,
							"question": "If you could be any animal, which one would you be and why?",
							"answer": "Animal?  I be Elmo."
						},
						{
							"rating": 2,
							"question": "What do you like to do for fun?",
							"answer": "I freeze."
						},
						{
							"rating": 3,
							"question": "Tell about a funny time in your life.",
							"answer": "Yesterday I had a binky.  I a elephant!"
						},
						{
							"rating": 2,
							"question": "What is your favorite thing to do? Why?",
							"answer": "Go church."
						},
						{
							"rating": 1,
							"question": "What is your favorite thing to do with your friends?",
							"answer": "Gabba Gabba!"
						},
						{
							"rating": 3,
							"question": "What do you love most about your siblings?",
							"answer": "Tony here Tony (points to Tony in a picture).  (\"Harmony?\") That one!  (then points to Angel) Angel!"
						},
						{
							"rating": 1,
							"question": "What was the nicest thing you did for someone?",
							"answer": "Six.  (\"Six?\")  Yeah, six."
						},
						{
							"rating": 2,
							"question": "What do you think you will be doing 10 years from now?",
							"answer": "Milk.... (Points to her bowl of cereal) This is milk."
						},
						{
							"rating": 1,
							"question": "What is your favorite thing to do in the summer?",
							"answer": "Summer... hiding (she hides under the chair)."
						},
						{
							"rating": 3,
							"question": "What would be the ideal allowance? Tell me how you would use it.",
							"answer": "Fish. (\"Fish?\") Yeah, fish."
						},
						{
							"rating": 2,
							"question": "What do you think makes a person good-looking?",
							"answer": "My teeth."
						},
						{
							"rating": 1,
							"question": "How do you think peanut butter is made?",
							"answer": "Brush a hair."
						},
						{
							"rating": 2,
							"question": "What does Daddy do at work?",
							"answer": "Daddy at work a Elmo."
						},
						{
							"rating": 1,
							"question": "How do you think shows get onto the TV?",
							"answer": "TV a Gabba Gabba."
						},
						{
							"rating": 1,
							"question": "What do you think Yo Gabba Gabba do when they're not on TV?",
							"answer": "TV!  Hahaha!"
						}
					]
				},
				{
					"qDate": "2014-08-17",
					"questions": [
						{
							"rating": 2,
							"question": "What is your happiest memory?",
							"answer": "My happiest memory is giving Daddy a card"
						},
						{
							"rating": 3,
							"question": "Why do you like being a kid?",
							"answer": "Because I can said letters to Dad, like cards and stuff. Cause I love Daddy"
						},
						{
							"rating": 3,
							"question": "One word to describe you would be _______.",
							"answer": "Giving Dad notes"
						},
						{
							"rating": 1,
							"question": "What advice would you give your parents?",
							"answer": "Give cards"
						},
						{
							"rating": 3,
							"question": "If you could be any animal, which one would you be and why?",
							"answer": "I would be a giraffe in the race game because it has a lot of health"
						},
						{
							"rating": 1,
							"question": "What do you like to do for fun?",
							"answer": "Play Pikmin"
						},
						{
							"rating": 3,
							"question": "Tell about a funny time in your life.",
							"answer": "Telling jokes. I laugh so hard, water comes out my eyes"
						},
						{
							"rating": 3,
							"question": "What is your favorite thing to do? Why?",
							"answer": "Playing the iPad. Because they make a swatch movie and God forgave our sin so we can be in heaven."
						},
						{
							"rating": 1,
							"question": "What is your favorite thing to do with your friends?",
							"answer": "Play tag"
						},
						{
							"rating": 2,
							"question": "What do you love most about your siblings?",
							"answer": "Angel: her tea parties; Tony: playing games, like Pikmin; Harmony: King of the Castle; Chase: playing run around the rosie"
						},
						{
							"rating": 1,
							"question": "What was the nicest thing you did for someone?",
							"answer": "Play with them"
						},
						{
							"rating": 3,
							"question": "What do you think you will be doing 10 years from now?",
							"answer": "Playing hide n seek"
						},
						{
							"rating": 2,
							"question": "What is your favorite thing to do in the summer?",
							"answer": "Sending celebrations and opening presents"
						},
						{
							"rating": 3,
							"question": "What would be the ideal allowance? Tell me how you would use it.",
							"answer": "$2000. I would use it to pay the bank"
						},
						{
							"rating": 2,
							"question": "What do you think makes a person good-looking?",
							"answer": "Playing and napping"
						},
						{
							"rating": 1,
							"question": "Name two things we should do as a family on the weekend.",
							"answer": "Play puzzles, play with cars, and Harmony"
						},
						{
							"rating": 2,
							"question": "What is the grossest thing you can think of?",
							"answer": "Really stinky pie"
						}
					]
				}
			]
		},
		{
			"name": "Chase",
			"fullName": "Chase Alexander Moritz",
			"birthday": "2012-07-20",
			"questionnaires": [
				{
					"qDate": "2012-07-20",
					"questions": [
						{
							"rating": 3,
							"question": "Hi little guy!",
							"answer": "Waa! Waa! Waaaaaaa!!!"
						}
					]
				},
				{
					"qDate": "2014-08-17",
					"questions": [
						{
							"rating": 3,
							"question": "What do you think makes a person good-looking?",
							"answer": "A ball!"
						}
					]
				}
			]
		}
	]
}
